Collaboration wins
What's the big thing that happened recently?
Big event? I don't have that much work anymore.
Anything? You know, something at work that made you happy?
Yes, I do.
Any sense of accomplishment?
First of all, I completed my first tour.
And I did that while working on TV and all that.
You're practicing now?
I've been working hard.
After it was over?
Yes, yes, yes.
First of all, it was an accomplishment for me to be able to do that.
And then rocking.
Rocking.
You got it?
Yeah. Doing the bird.
That was amazing.
To be able to perform in front of 20,000 people.
And then we did the uterus ceremony.
So you had a uterine ceremony.
It was a lot of fun.
That was a big event.
I'm glad you didn't get sick.
What's it like being in front of 20,000 people?
Oh, man.
I don't know.
Does it feel good?
It feels so good.It feels so good.
I love it.
Music and live performances are so much fun.
If you were going to do a live show by yourself, where would you want to end up?
I didn't have that in mind.
But seeing 20,000 people...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So until a little while ago, I thought it didn't matter where.
But I'd like to do it at Budokan or some historic place like that.
Recently, I've finally decided to do it at the Budokan.
That's great.
You've already decided.
I haven't decided anything.
You know, venues like that are decided long before anything is decided.
You're right.
It's not a hint.
No, it's not.
It's important to have fans in order to be able to do that.
I can't do it by myself.
I want to go.
If you're going to do the Budokan, please invite me.
I'm sure you'll do what you're doing.
I want you to come.
I want to see it.
I want you to see me live.
I think it'll be fun.
You're going to see it?
Yes, I will.
I'd love to.
There's a lot of runway and stuff.Isn't there an awful lot of runway and stuff?
Sort of.
It's like a festival.
That's why not everyone is a fan of ours.
That's why, as I told you when we met for work.
I want to be a born again artist.
It's a different kind of influence.
It's different.
The number of fans we can call our own is probably limited to 1,000.
If you say it like that...
If you say it in real life...
That's right.
We don't even have our own songs.
I've done it once before.
If it was a regular event, not a live performance, it would be more...
But then again, maybe not everyone is that interested in the world.
It's so negative.
We put a lot of effort into it, but it's only 1,000 people.
But singing has the power to reach so many people.
I really envy you for being able to gather thousands and thousands of people.
I didn't expect that.
I almost got good at singing.
What a surprise.
You like to stand out.
From my point of view...
I can't do that runway thing.
I can't do that.
I can't.
I think it's really cool.
Walking down the runway with all these people watching.Walking proudly with all these people watching.
Leave some for me.
Oh, yeah.
What's wrong with that?
What's that?
How did you practice?
But maybe some of the older guys were watching.
Look at it like this, with the center of gravity a little to the right.
Leave it like this.
Like, "Oh, that's how it's supposed to be done.
Are you self-taught?
I'm self-taught, so the first one is totally terrible.
Is that part of it?
Yes, that's part of it.
That's part of it.
I'm self-taught, so the first ones are pretty bad.
Plus, you've done variety shows.
Variety?
I enjoy variety.
But I don't think I'm cut out for it.
You're definitely cut out for it.
No, no, no, I'm not cut out for this.
Like, when Miko's around.
When there's a bunch of people around.
I don't know if it's right for me to be in a place like this.
I could cry at the Osaka Enkoudoukai.
Isn't it great that you're having so much fun? Emotionally.
That's amazing.
That made me so happy.
It was fun, wasn't it?It was fun, wasn't it?
We were so happy to be on the same team.
I didn't go to school at all.
I'm an adult now.
It's fun to be young with everyone.
You tend to think that everyone is awkward.
People who watch TV tend to think it's between women.
That's true.
I didn't think so.
I was so happy that she was so nice to me.
I felt like she was nice to me.
She was nice to me.
How have you lived with that?
You haven't been treated well?
Yeah, it was nice.
It's a variety. It's fun.
I hope I get to see you again sometime.
I've never seen you outside of an argument.
It'd be fun to see you again.
But even if we did, you'd forget all this.
I won't.
You're surprisingly talkative, aren't you?
You're not going back to zero, are you?
You're the type to go back to zero.
I do.
I'm the type that goes back.
We might think something is wrong with each other.
No!
The Collector is here. Similarity.
This is totally unrelated, but what are you spending your money on?Not that it matters at all, but what are you spending your money on?
I mean, it's really...
You don't seem to spend it.
No, I don't have time to spend it.
I mean, it's like, you know, instruments or clothes or...
And then it's gone.
Gone?
It's going to be gone soon.
Really? Even though we're doing a lot of commercials right now?
Yeah.
They're gonna run out? How many are you buying?
I buy a lot.
I thought you didn't use it at all.
I spend a lot.
I'm not really good at saving money.
You don't?
No.
I have to save for my future.
Do you save?
Yeah, I'm saving.
Really?
There's a line where I'm saving.
I'm saving this amount.
I'm not gonna mess with this.
Because you never know when something might shake loose in this house.
I might not be at this job tomorrow.
That's right.
I'll save the money to play it back then.
That's great.
It's good to save it.You can keep it, though.
I'd keep it, though.
But if I'm left with zero money or something...
Even if I quit this job with zero yen in my pocket.
I'm thinking I can manage somehow.
Maybe you can do it, Ano.
I think I can manage.
I don't know.
This sucks.
What are you doing?
Tomorrow, or rather, today, is the end of entertainment.
And don't use the name "Ano.
I want to do construction and road maintenance.
Do you really want to do that?
I'm sure you're just kidding.
I think it'd be really cool.
Sweatshop type.
I don't know, this job nowadays...
You have to care a little bit about your looks.
Like, you have to worry about your bangs.
I want something without all that.
Road maintenance? Start my life over?
Yes, sir.
But if you had to start over...
If you had to start over, what would you do?
Well, don't go get your license.
Oh, YouCan.
YouCan?
Sure, I'll do that.
I like puppies.I love dogs.
I'm thinking of becoming a certified trimmer.
I'm thinking of going out to the country and cutting dogs.
Might be a good idea.
A dog might be nice.
I like animals too.
A zoo would be nice.
What do you like? I like red pandas.
Panda.
Pandas? Are we close?
Close.
Do you like red pandas?
Have you ever really wanted to own a red panda?
It's true, I can't keep animals.
You don't have any right now? At home?
I don't have any animals at home right now.
I live alone.
I live alone. I can't keep an animal when I'm out of town for a gig.
I'd feel sorry for you.
I'll keep her if she can live with someone.
I don't know what to ask you, Anna.
You can ask.
I'll just use what I can.
Are you going on a date?
Do you?
I mean, right now, with this girl.
What if she knows?
She knows so much about you now.You're so well known now.
I'm talking about the last year or two.
Have you been on any dates?
No.
No?
I can't date.
Why not?
I really don't have time.
I don't have time.
I don't go out by myself, so I don't have much time.
No?
I don't really like to go anywhere.
So you're a stay-at-home type.
I prefer to stay at home.
Which do you prefer?
You want to go to the park or you want to stay at home?
I could go either way.
If it's a house, I'd make popcorn.
That's so cute.
I'd stay home.
We could watch a movie.
But I also like to go outside.
You had a date outside?
I had a date outside.
Did they stab you in the face?
Surprisingly.
If you talk, they'll know, but if you wear a hat, they won't.
The cinema at Roppongi Hills is nice.Roppongi Hills movie theater is good.
0 and small rounded.
Oh, yeah.
There's one nice parking lot, and once you park, you can take the elevator straight to the movie theater floor.
I can't follow you!
Maybe a picture.
There's a chance they'll take a picture, but you can get to the movie theater without wandering around too much.
I used to go there all the time.
Good information.
I had a similar question.
Are you an outdoorsman? Indoorsy?
You're definitely an indoor person, right?
Definitely an indoor person.
You never go outside?
What about your friends? You don't go out?
I go out sometimes, but only when I'm on the way to dinner.
Does that count as outdoor?
Indoor?
I don't go outside much.
You don't?
I mean, I'm sure I'd get stabbed in the face a lot, but I don't know if it would bother you.
What about being photographed? What do you do?
I don't have to worry about being filmed.
Can you go? Oh, my God.
Okay, how are you doing?
He looks really down.
And you look sad.
No, but you don't like it.
I don't like it.
I don't like it. I don't like it.I don't like it. I don't like it.
But I wouldn't say it either.
I'd rather take a picture with you.
If someone asked you to take a picture with them, would you take it?
I wouldn't.
I wouldn't take a picture either.
On the other hand, it would lead to the fans.
You're spending all that money on a fan girl.
Yeah, it's the same thing.
You're taking pictures.
If you put something on there and say you took Nicole's picture...
I feel so sorry for the fan girl.
I told her to come to the event.
I don't like it when fans pay to have their pictures taken.
I didn't like it.
I told him it's okay if he takes spy photos.
That's new.
That's a new kind of open-mindedness.
I'll walk.
I used to do that.
On the other hand, when I still wanted to sell.
I'd intentionally walk down Takeshita Street.
I wanted to make myself known.
I'd get approached and have my picture taken.
When I didn't have any fans yet.
That's right.
You have a lot of ambition and ambition, don't you?
Yes, I do.
I like to be number one in everything.
Oh, I see.Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
You know, magazines, popularity... they have to have a number one.
I don't want to be number two.
I want to be number one.
I hate to lose.
That's right.
Oh, I didn't know that.
I like to be first in everything.
Oh, did you put yourself in first place at Lohan?
You did.
And I came in second.
And you came in second.
Yes, I came in second.
Yes, I'm negative, but I kind of like myself.
Mm-hmm.
I like first place.
I hate being in the middle.
First place is good.
Hey.
You ever come in first in anything?
Anything.
I used to run track in elementary school.
So you're fast.
Yeah, I won first place in a city meet.
That's amazing.
With those hurdles.
You're an athlete.
But you were so good on the exam.
I used to play softball too.We used to play softball too.
Oh, wow!
We have strong shoulders.
I didn't know that.
I played in a testing game once... and I got no bounces.
That's amazing.
I'm not like that.
Really.
I'm not good at any of the Longhorns' athletic events, but if it's shoulder stuff, I'd be first in my class.
If you have something like this to throw...
That's right.
I'm really good at dodgeball.
Aim for the feet.
I want to play dodgeball at Longhorns.
Sure, sure.
I like dodgeball, too.
I'd love to.
Michyopa is strong, too.
She seems strong.
Yes, she is.
Looks like she can throw a fastball.
Yeah, we'll do it like this, too.
I wonder...
Gals are athletic to begin with, aren't they?
You're probably right.
That's amazing.
Are they active?
Yeah.
I wonder if she's active.I wonder if he's active.
I wonder why that is.
The last one?
The last one.
If you two were going on location together, what would you do?
What do you want to do?
Well, I don't know.
But I'd like to experience your culture.
What's your culture?
What kind of culture?
I don't know.
It's a history.
Beef history?
Okiroki.
I originally came from Nicoleenbeam's place.
I'm probably from the opposite end of the spectrum.
Now we talk to each other.
But back then, I don't think we would have been involved.
That's what we show each other.
Do you want to do that?
So we have to be like you?
I can't. I can't sing.
So we trade? Occupation?
Occupation.
I'm sure your fans would kill me.
And maybe some dodgeball.
I know.
I want to do a dodgeball shoot.
You sure? You want to play dodgeball?
I want to play dodgeball.I want to play dodgeball.
I want to go to Spo-cha.
I've never been to a Pachinko and Pachinko parlor.
No? No? It'll be fun.
It's not my life.
I want to go.
I see.
I want to go to the spo-cha.
Spo-cha, bowling, basketball, ballet...
You can do that much?
It's got a purikura machine.
Do you go to the sports hall often?
I go to Spo-cha a lot.
Then tell me about it.
Sure.
That's it.
Let's go to Spo-cha.
Spo-cha or pachinko? You could teach me pachinko.
I'll teach you pachinko.
I want to try pachinko.
But I don't want you to get addicted.
You can play by yourself.
You don't need friends to play.
That's right.
There are lots of anime machines.
Like Evangirion.
Rizero...
Rizero.
And Gundam.
Gundam.Gundam
Something a little...
There's something here.
There's a pachinko machine at the Takasugi Clinic.
What?
Yes, there is.
That Dr. Takas.
That's right.
Pachinko might be nice.
Let's go play pachinko.
Let's go to Spo-Cha.
We'll go to Spo-Cha and then we'll go to Pachinko.
Spo-cha.
We'll go to Pachinko and then to Spo-Cha?
Let's go twice.
Yes, two times.
I want to go to Spo-Cha once in my life.
Let's go with this.
Play.
I want you to play.
I don't care if it's private, but pachinko.
Sure, pachinko is private.
You don't have to talk.
Just stand next to me.
You don't have to say much.
When I hit a jackpot...
Oh, that's a nice touch.
Yeah, it's good. It's good.
I'd appreciate that.
That would be nice.That might be a good idea.
It's on from morning till night.
If there's anything on that channel, it's Spo-cha.
Private pachinko.
Worst story ever.
I'm looking forward to it.
It's good.
Oh, my God.
Can I invite my mom over? For the slingshot.
I'd love to.
I'll go with my mom. I'll call her.
I'll call her, too.
Will you tell her that?
But you'll have to produce the clothes and stuff.
It's a lot of work.
Oh, my God.
What about that? I mean, not a brand, but a collaboration.
Because with clothes, we have to work once a week.
You're tied up for hours and have to think about it all the time.
There are meetings for sure.
We have more meetings than recordings now.
We have too many things to do.
I can't do that now.
I can't do that.
I can't do it even if it's what the fans want.
They say that? I have to lay down my role.
I'll be told.
I'm a professional. I'm a professional at producing.
I want to do it. I'm doing it.
You've changed from your previous brand, haven't you?You changed from the previous brand, didn't you?
Yes, I did.
That's great, too.
I'm changing. I'm changing what I like.
The brand I made when I was a teenager and the type of clothes I wear change when I'm over 20.
So I change my brand because I wear the clothes that suit me at that time.
I think that's great too.
Isn't that a lot of work?
That's for sure.
I was looking at her and thinking how well she was doing.
I mean, you've got fans coming to you like this.
Wouldn't it be great if you could do it all with your own stuff?
That would be the best.
Your own clothes, your own cosmetics, your own clothes.
You know, it would make the fans happy if it's all done by you.
And I think that's the best.
She's a strong woman.
I like people like that.
I think people with a core like that are cool.
It fills me up inside when I see someone like that.
That's great.
I'm the type of person who thinks, "That's so cool!
I'm the type of person who thinks
That's why I wanted to be with him.
I thought about that Koyama producer.
Maro-chan's cool too, doing what he wants to do.
Working hard and making everyone happy.
That's good.
You're working hard.
He gave me a compliment.You gave me a compliment.
Do you think that's great? I'm always on social media.
Sometimes you lose your temper.
You do lose your temper.
That's funny.
Should I keep doing that?
- No, it's not good? No, it's not good? No, it's not good, is it?
- But you know what?
- It's always been there, hasn't it?
- No, I understand.
- Always.
- I used to tweet more about what I was thinking.
But I want you to stay the same.
I feel like you're speaking for me.
- I'm glad.
- I'm glad you like my tweets.
- I'll tweet from now on.
- I'll tweet instead of you.
And get flamed instead.
- No, you don't.
It's all on the Internet.
- It's all over the Internet.
That really pisses me off, doesn't it?
- I know...
Sometimes, at the end...
The name of the person who took care of it
I always take a picture of it
I thought, "This is the guy.
- I think you must be obsessed with it, or frustrated by it.
I'm sure Nicole must have a lot of frustration.Nicole, I'm sure there will be a lot of it.
- I'll watch the whole baked goods thing.
- I'll look at all the comments.
- I'll look at all of them, even if they're in red.
- Oh, 2,000 comments?
- I'll look at all the comments, even if they're all red.
- What do you do when you see that? What do you do with it?
- Look at it and absorb it.
Absorb it.
You look at it and you absorb it, and then you go, "Hmm.
- What if it says something sad?
- Sometimes it's nothing.
But it's like a bonfire.
- Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
You know what I mean?
- It makes you stronger.
But surprisingly... there are times when you're right.
- I know, I know
- I know, I know, it looks that way to the world
So I'll fix this part
- I look at it too.
I don't look at everything.
I look at it a lot.
- What do you do?
- That's what I do.
- Same thing?
- I feel like shit.
I feel like I'm looking back at it.
I don't know.
Because people who haven't seen the show are saying that.It's coming from people who haven't really looked at it properly.
- Yeah, this one in a nutshell.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You're gonna say, "Fuck.
- I'm going to be a dick.
- And I don't like it when people write about it.
I don't want the story to get written up. I want the story to get written up.
- Yeah, that's the way it is.
On my profile, on my Instagram profile.
- I know, I know.
- What's a story? Like, no stories.
- Only Nicole would write something like that.
- Did they know?
- She knows.
- Yes, they know. If I write that, I can't really do anything.
The stories disappear in 24 hours.
And you've been posting them.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- I don't understand why it's on the Internet news.
- I don't get it.
- That's why I put it in my profile.
So I put it in my profile and now it's not.
Why don't you write it?
Let's make it matching.
- No, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
- Lame? Lame?
- I mean, it's not tacky or anything, but...
- I mean, it's not like it's tacky or anything, but is it tacky to put on your profile?
- No, but if it works, maybe.- No, but if it works, maybe.
If it doesn't work, writing about it...
- If it doesn't work, I'll think you're a pain in the ass.
- I'm just going to go write about it.
- Well, try it for the rest of the year.
- Um, story.
- You're not allowed to post it in the story.
- That might be a good idea.
- I don't know what that means.
- I'm going to start tweeting.
Nicole has everything I have to say.
Is that okay?
- I'll leave it with you.
- Are you sure?
- Yes, really?
- I trust you.
I'll do it for you.
- I'll do it for you.
- Common ground.
We have a lot in common.
- You're working hard.
I don't know if I should say this, but...
She cares about her fans.
- She cares about her fans.
She says what she wants to say.
- I mean, you're honest.
I'm not lying.There is no lie.
- No lies.
It's wonderful.
- Excellent.
- How was it?
- No, it was fun.
- No, it was fun. It was fun. I don't feel like I could speak without an opportunity like this.
- There was something to absorb.
- I did. Me too.
- But there wasn't much of a gap.
- She was the girl we thought she was. The way she thinks...
- Oh, really?
- I thought she was really cool, too.
- I still don't understand why he likes her face so much.
- I like her face, too. I like his face too. I like her face too. She's cute.
- Please come again. Corrises.
- Please call me.
- I won't.
- He's a bit tedious.
- He asks me a lot of questions, and if I'm too lazy to answer, then I'm not going to give him a NG.
- I'm grateful that he only asks me for interviews.
- I'd like to go to the Budokan anyway.
- I want to go to the Budokan. If you can make it.
- Yes, I can. I don't mean if you can.
- If you can?
- I can do it.
- I'll do it. I'll do it. - Okay, then.
- Congratulations on your wedding.
- Thank you.
- Properly amazing. It's my favorite color yellow.- Properly amazing. It's my favorite color yellow.
- Yellow.
- Amazing. Thank you.
- That's Pokemon!
- Pokemon!
- What?
- What? What's this?
- Oh, here you go.
- Oh, wow.
- Wait a minute. I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared.
- It's a Pokemon cake.
- It's a cake. Thank you.
- Cute.
- Congratulations on your wedding.
- Thank you.
- Married. Awesome.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- That's great.
- Nothing's changed, though. Not really.
- Nothing. - Yeah.
- Eh. Thank you very much.
- Please subscribe to that channel.
I feel like I could be someone.